So in this module,
-: إذن في هذه الوحدة
we had a look at react and TypeScript.
، ألقينا نظرة على رد فعل و TypeScript.
And as you see TypeScript here again,
وكما ترى TypeScript هنا
can add a lot of nice extra features and checks,
مرة أخرى ، يمكن أن تضيف الكثير من الميزات الإضافية والتحقق اللطيف
that make sure that we write clear and error free code.
، والتي تتأكد من أننا نكتب رمزًا واضحًا وخاليًا من الأخطاء.
Now, I did show you a couple of
الآن ، لقد عرضت لك بعض الأنماط
very important patterns there,
المهمة جدًا هناك ، واثنين من
and a couple of very important React features
ميزات React المهمة جدًا مثل Props
like Props and State, and how to use them with TypeScript.
و State ، وكيفية استخدامها مع TypeScript.
I also showed you how you should think about
لقد أوضحت لك أيضًا كيف يجب أن تفكر
adding our functionalities like Redux,
في إضافة وظائفنا مثل Redux ، والتي
which we didn't use in this module.
لم نستخدمها في هذه الوحدة.
And as I also mentioned,
وكما ذكرت أيضًا ، في
at the end of the last lecture,
نهاية المحاضرة الأخيرة ،
don't forget about all the other things
لا تنسَ كل الأشياء الأخرى التي تعلمتها
you learned about in this course.
في هذه الدورة.
All the types you learned about,
كل الأنواع التي تعلمتها ، وكل الأشياء
and all the things you can do with TypeScript.
التي يمكنك القيام بها باستخدام TypeScript.
Including the configuration here.
بما في ذلك التكوين هنا.
Everything you learned applies to this React,
كل ما تعلمته ينطبق على React هذا ، بالإضافة
plus TypeScript project as well.
إلى مشروع TypeScript أيضًا.
Just because we had a nice configuration,
فقط لأن لدينا تكوينًا رائعًا ،
out of the box here, does not mean that you can't tweak it.
خارج الصندوق هنا ، لا يعني أنه لا يمكنك تعديله.
You can tweak it, and you can use everything
يمكنك تعديله ، ويمكنك استخدام كل ما تعلمته في
you learned in this course here in this project.
هذه الدورة التدريبية هنا في هذا المشروع.
Because after all, even though
لأنه بعد كل شيء ، على الرغم من أننا
we're writing some React-ish code,
نكتب بعض التعليمات البرمجية React-ish
and we can use JSX, we're still writing JavaScript
، ويمكننا استخدام JSX ، ما زلنا نكتب JavaScript أو رمز TypeScript
or specifically TypeScript code.
على وجه التحديد.
And therefore everything you learn throughout course,
وبالتالي فإن كل ما تتعلمه خلال الدورة التدريبية
is valid here as well.
صالح هنا أيضًا.
It's easy to forget that, so always keep it in mind.
من السهل نسيان ذلك ، لذلك ضع ذلك دائمًا في الاعتبار.
And with that, consider creating
وبهذا ، ضع في اعتبارك إنشاء مشروع
your next React project with TypeScript.
React التالي باستخدام TypeScript.
You now certainly know, how to get started and how it works.
أنت تعرف الآن بالتأكيد كيف تبدأ وكيف تعمل.